

## MD JAHID HASAN

#### **FULL STACK WEB DEVELOPER**

Please visit my portfolio

Website: jahid-facts.github.io





**Phone** 01762703065



## **EXPERTISE**

- Flutter
- Dart
- Laravel
- PHP
- WordPress
- JavaScript
- Bootstrap
- CSS
- HTML
- Adobe Photoshop
- Adobe Illustrator

## **PROFILE**



I am Md Jahid Hasan. I am a Full Stack Web Developer from Bangladesh with one year plus job experience.

I generally like to take on new challenges and want to try new things. I love to solve complex problems. I usually use HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, JavaScript, and jQuery for frontend design and PHP, and Laravel for the backend. I have worked in Fiverr & Freelancer international marketplace—also have basic knowledge of Graphic Design.

I am very dedicated to my work. I try to do my work on time at any cost.

### PERSONAL SKILLS

- Team Work
- · Problem-solving skills
- Creative thinking skills
- Time management skills

## **WORK EXPERIENCE**



**Junior Programmer** 

IPSITA COMPUTERS PTE LTD.

JAN 2023 - PRESENT

I am working as a junior developer in this company. Here we provide all types of web application design and development for our clients. Such as ecommerce web applications, inventory management systems, etc



English Bangla Hindi



A

**Industrial Attachment** 

IPSITA COMPUTERS PTE LTD. 10 OCT 2022 - 9 JAN 2023

Learned HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, JavaScript, and jQuery for frontend design and PHP, Laravel for backend, and developed one project.

## **EDUCATION**

## WORK EXPERIENCE

#### **Diploma in Engineering**

VISION POLYTECHNIC INSTITUTE KURIGRAM 2018 - 2023

Technology: Computer Engineering
Dhaka Board

## **Secondary School Certificate**

SONALUR KUTI HIGH SCHOOL, 2018

Group : Science Dinajpur Board 

# Web Design , Development & Graphics Design WWW.FIVERR.COM NOV 2019

My account is a level-one seller on Fiverr. I have successfully completed many projects with positive feedback.

#### Web Design & Development

LEARNING & EARNING DEVELOPMENT PROJECT | ICT DIVISION AUG 2020

Core skill 1. HTML, CSS, Javascript, PHP, WordPress website development, 1. Marketplace Deployment.

## **PROJECTS**



#### **Arsha**

Link:

https://jahid-facts.github.io/Arsha/

#### **FlexStart**

Link:

https://jahid-facts.github.io/FlexStart/

#### Logis

Link:

https://jahid-facts.github.io/Logis/

#### **Job Portal**

Link:

https://jahid-facts.github.io/job-portal/

## **PROJECTS**



## **Ipsita Computers Pte Ltd.**

**Link:** www.ipsitasoft.com/

IPSITA COMPUTERS PTE LTD is one of the pioneer Information Technology Companies in Bangladesh started journey in the year of 1994.

. G

#### **Minimum Maximum Health Care Foundation**

**Link:** www.minimaxhealthcare.org/

Minimax Healthcare Foundation is a non-profit, non-political, and public service initiative. The aim of the foundation is to ensure the highest quality healthcare at a minimum cost to the beneficiaries.



#### Gaanganala

Link: www.gaanjanala.com/

It is a music-related website dealing with all types of music.

## COURSE

Web Design & Development
 Learning & Earning Development
 Project | ICT Division Aug 2020

Diploma in Computer Engineering

Vision Polytechnic Institute, Kurigram 2018 - 2023



#### **Bangladesh Business Chamber of Singapore (BDCham).**

**Link:** http://bdcham.ipsitacomputersltd.com/

A multicultural and multiracial business and a financial hub much sought after by foreign investors around the world, thanks to its efficient and competent leadership and government.